VLADYSLAV CHEKHOVSKIY

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



v.chek1218@gmail.com

Onipro, Ukraine

PROFILE

Developer with more than 1 year of experience. I create websites with different levels of complexity and a set of tasks. Thereby trying to introduce new technologies into the project. The immediate goal is to form a further career in the IT industry, and develop experience in new projects.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- SASS/SCSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- TypeScript
- Git
- Node.js

EDUCATION

Dnipro National Univesity

Sep, 2020 - Present

Specialty computer technology, I study in the first year.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Dgym Company

Okt, 2022 - Mar, 2023

Throughout my work, my responsibility was the development of websites of varying complexity and their structure.

FREELANCE

Apr, 2022 - Okt, 2022

- Creation of websites from scratch
- Development of site structure
- Negoatiations with client
- Additional features and improvements to the finished site